Guide to The Leo Deaner Radical Left-Wing Publications collection, 1890-2017 LAC0011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Pamphlets by title: New Left [arrangement alphabetical], 1960-2007; bulk; Series 2
  - "Revolutionary Committees as a Method of Organization", 1973; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Published by More To Come.
  - "Revolutionary Union: Opportunism in a 'Super-Revolutionary' Disguise", 1974 December; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Published by the October League M-L.
  - "Revolutionary Work in a Non-Revolutionary Situation", 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - "The Rise and Fall of the 'Gang of Four'", 1977; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Author: Hsin Chi. Published by Books New China, Inc. Chinese publications.
  - Ronald Reagan, 1984; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Reagan, Ronald
  - "RSU Anti-Imperialist Newsletter", 1973 March 6; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Published by the Radical Student Union.
    Radical Student Union (University of California, Berkeley); University of California, Berkeley
  - Ruchell Magee, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - "Sacramento Delta Blues: Chinese Workers and the Building of the California Levees, 1860-1880", undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    China
  - San Diego Convention Coalition, 1972; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ) -- 1960-1970.
  - The San Quentin Six, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - "The Save the Steps Rally: A Complete Transcript of the Speeches", 1966; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Published by Academic Publishing.
    Freedom of speech -- United States; Free Speech Movement (Berkeley, Calif.)
  - "SDS Bulletin", 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "SDS and Educational Reform", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Author: Michael Rossman.
  - "SDS and the Movement", 1969 September; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Authors: Jack Weinberg and Jack Gerson.
  - "SDS Plans for America's High Schools", 1969; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Report by the Committee on Internal Security, House of Representatives.
  - "SDS Work-In 1968: Towards a Worker-Student Alliance", Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - "Seize the Time" Newspaper, 1974-1977; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - "Selected Articles Criticizing Lin Piao and Confucius", 1975; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "Sex Symbol", undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Published by the Red Women's Detatchment of the Marxist-Leninist Party.
  - "Social Imperialism", 1970s; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Reprints from Peking Review. Chinese publications.
  - Socialist Organizing Committee, Orange County California, 1977; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; Socialist Organizing Committee (Orange County, Calif.)
  - "Socialism and the Intellectuals", 1967; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Author: Paul Lafargue. Published by New York Labor News.
  - Soledad Brothers Legal Fund, 1971; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "Songs for Peace", undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - "Soviet Naval Strategy", 1977; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Authors: Dirk Hennings and Alexandra Herrman.
    Soviet Union
  - "Soviet Social Imperialism in India", 1976 June 26; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Published by the Communist Party of India (M-L).
    India; New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism
  - "Soviets in Italy", undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Author: Antonio Gramsci.
    Gramsci, Antonio, 1891-1937
  - "The Spectrum" State University of New York at Buffalo Newspaper, 1970 May 8; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States; Student movements; Protest movements
  - "Speech by Chiao Kuan-Hua, Chairman of the Delegation of the People's Republic of China at the Plenary Meeting of the 27th Session of the UN General Assembly", 1972; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - "Speech by Chairman of the Delegation of the People's Republic of China, Teng Hsiao-Ping, At the Special Session of the UN General Assembly", 1974; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - "St. Louis Outlaw" Newspaper, 1970 September; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "Stalin, Marxism-Leninism and the Left", 1976; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    Author: Russell Jacoby. Published by New England Free Press.
  - "Stalin's Speeches on the American Communist Party", undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Marxism-Leninism
  - "Statement by the Revolutionary Union on Building a Multi-National Organization", 1974 June 15; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - "Statements of Draft Resisters", 1967 July 28; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    Published by the New England Committee for Nonviolent Action.
    Draft resisters
  - "Stay In, Build a Campus SDS!!", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - "Steps: Journal of the Free University of Berkeley", 1966; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - "Stop Rizzo: The Rise of a Would-Be Dictator", 1978; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    Philadelphia (Pa.)
  - "Stop Runaway Shops", 1981; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    Published by the Citizens Labor Committee on Plant Closures.
  - "Stop the Trial, Free Bobby!" Youth International Party Flyer, 1971; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    Youth International Party
  - "Strike!", 1965 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Published by the Socialist Party of Ohio.
    Socialist Party of Ohio
  - "Strive for New Victories", 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - "Struggle Against Drugs!", undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    Published by the United Front Against Imperialism.
  - "The Struggle Against Revisionism and Opportunism: Against the Communist League and the Revolutionary Union", 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Marxism-Leninism; New Communist movement; Black Workers Congress
  - "The Struggle Against Teng Hsiao-Ping's Revisionist Line", 1977 July; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "The Struggle Between the Two Roads in China's Countryside", 1968; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Published by Foreign Language Press. Chinese publications.
  - "The Struggle to Free Gary Tyler", 1976 October; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Published by the October League (M-L).
  - "The Struggle Inside", 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    University of California Berkeley Prison Action Conference Pauley Ballroom
    Prisons -- United States; University of California, Berkeley; Radical Student Union (University of California, Berkeley)
  - "Student Government Brochure", undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    University is not identified. [donor indicates that maybe it was in Dayton Ohio]
  - Student Mobilizing Committee (SMC), 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Folder contains various flyers concerning Anti-war demonstrations October 15, 31 and November 13
  - "Students and Revolution", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Authors: Roxanne Dunbar and Vernon Grizzard.
  - Students for a Democratic Society Flyers, 1960s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "Study Guide on the New Left", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Author: Hal Benenson. Published by Students for a Democratic Society.
  - "Study Philosophy: Reprints from Peking Review", 1966; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - "Sun Dance" Magazine, 1972; Series 2 (Oversize 18, Folder 1)
  - "Tachai: The Red Banner", 1977; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Taching: Red Banner on China's Industrial Front", 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Published by Foreign Langauges Press. Chinese publications
  - "Talkin' Union: Music, Lore, History", 1985 December; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Labor unions
  - Teng Hsiao-Ping and the 'General Program'", 1977; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Published by Red Sun Publishers. Chinese publications.
  - "Terrorism - Is it Revolutionary?", 1970 July; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Author: Gil Green. Published by New Outlook Publishers.
  - "Their Struggle is Our Struggle", undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Published by the Black Workers Congress and the Revolutionary Union.
    New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; Black Workers Congress; Revolutionary Union
  - "Theoretical Review: A Journal of Marxist-Leninist Theory and Discussion", 1978 March-April; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "They're In for Us, We're Out for Them", 1970s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Prisons -- United States; New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; Revolutionary Union
  - "This is War? An Analysis of the War on Poverty with Special Emphasis on Appalachia", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Author: Robb Burlage. Published by Students for a Democratic Society.
  - "Throw the Bum Out!", 1970s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Published by the Workers Committee to Throw the Bum Out.
  - "A Time for Anger", 1973 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Author: Don West. Published by Appalachia Movement Press, Inc.
    Appalachian Region; New Left
  - "To the Black Community: Message from Jail, an Interview with Martin Sostre", 1967 August 1; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Published by the Martin Sostre Defense Committee.
    Black Liberation; National liberation movements; Civil rights; Prisons -- United States; Sostre, Martin, 1923-
  - "To the Marxist-Leninists, the Workers, and the Oppressed of all Countries", 1980; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Joint communique of international Communist organizations.
  - "To the Point...of Production: An Interview with John Watson", 1969; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Published by the Radical Education Project. Detroit Revolution Union Movement.
    Black Liberation
  - "To the Students at the University", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - "Toward Black Liberation", undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    Black Liberation; Civil rights; National liberation movements
  - "Toward the Working Class: A Position Paper for the New Left, Together with Why the Working Class?", 1966; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    "Toward the Working Class" by Kim Moody, Fred Eppsteiner, and Mike Flug. "Why the Working Class?" by Hal Draper. Published by the Independent Socialist Committee.
    Independent socialist
  - "Towards a New National Organization of the VDCs", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Author: Derrel Myers. Published by the Committee to End the War in Vietnam.
  - "Towards a Revolutionary Party: Ideas on Strategy and Organization", 1971 April; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Published by the Sojourner Truth Organization.
    Marxism-Leninism; New Communist movement; Sojourner Truth Organization
  - "Trade Union Question: A Communist Approach to Strategy, Tactics and Program", 1977; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Published by the Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee.
  - "The Truth About How the Leaders of the CPSU Have Allied Themselves with India Against China", 1963; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "The Tuparamos: Urban Guerrillas of Uruguay", 1970; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Author: Carlos Nunez. Published by Times Change Press.
  - "Two Roads: The Origins of the Sino-Soviet Dispute", 1974; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Author: Jack Scott. Published by New Star Books and Canada-China Friendship Association.
    New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; Canada
  - "The Two Superpowers: Main Enemies of the People of the World", 1976 August; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - "The Ultra-Left Danger and How to Fight It: Three Articles on 'Anti-Dogmatism' by the Proletarian Unity League", 1977; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Published by the Proletarian Unity League.
  - "Unemployed Councils in St. Petersburg in 1906", undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Author: Sergei Malyshev. Published by Proletarian Publishers.
  - "Unfinished Tasks of the Trade Union Education League", 1979; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Author: Dr. Philip S. Foner. Published by the Massachusetts Trade Union Education League.
  - "The Union Miners Cemetary", 1969; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Author: John Keiser. Published by the Illinois Labor History Society.
    Coal miners
  - United Front Against Imperialism Flyer, undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - "United the People, Defeat Our Enemies: Statement by the Revolutionary Union on the Shooting of George Wallace", 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - University of California at Berkeley Radical Student Union, 1972; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    The folder contains items listed: Blue Collar Worker's Strike and Demonstration Against Spiro Agnew in Palo Alto 1972
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States; University of California, Berkeley
  - "The Unknown Marx", 1968; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Author: Martin Nicolaus. Published by New England Free Press.
  - "Uruguay's Urban Guerrillas", 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Author: Marysa Gerassi. Reprinted from the New Left Review by the New England Free Press.
  - The Venceremos Brigade, 1976; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "A Veteran Communist Speaks", 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Author: Joe Dougher. Published by Proletarian Publishers.
  - "A Veteran Communist Speaks: Akron Rubber Workers' Strikes of 1936", 1975; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Author: Jim Keller. Published by Workers Press.
  - "A Veteran Communist Speaks: On the Struggle Against Revisionism", 1974; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Author: Admiral Kilpatrick. Published by the Communist League.
  - V.I. Lenin: "Karl Marx", 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - V.I. Lenin: "Socialism and War", undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Published by Foreign Languages Publishing House. Chinese publications.
  - "Victory through Our Struggle, Not through Elections!", 1970s; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Vietnam Study Guide and Annotated Bibliography", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Author: Steven Rosenthal. Published by Students for a Democratic Society.
    New Left; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States; Students for a Democratic Society (U.S.)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, 1970s; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States; Vietnam Veterans Against the War
  - The Vietnam War, 1965-1979; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    The folder contains three area group of mailers, flyers and a poster concerning Vietnamese students in the U.S.
  - "Wage Controls and How To Fight 'Em", 1973; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Published by the Workers Committee Against Wage Controls.
  - "War in the Coal Fields: The Northern Fields 1931", 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Author: WM. Z. Foster. Reprinted from the Labor Defender by Appalachian Movement Press, Inc.
  - "We Are Here: Songs of the Holocaust", 1983; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    Compiled by Eleanor Mlotek and Malke Gottlieb. Published by the Workingmen's Circle.
  - "We Need You - Become a Tenants Union Organizer", 1960s; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Published by the Berkeley Tenants Union.
  - "Weathermen-SDS Goes It (Very Much) Alone in 'Kick-Ass' Brawl", 1969 October 18; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Published in "Guardian" magazine.
  - Wei Min She (Organization for the People), undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; Wei Min SheÌ€
  - "The West Virginia Miners Union 1931", 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Author: Tom Tippett. Reprinted from Labor Age by Appalachian Movement Press, Inc.
    Appalachian Region; Coal miners
  - "What Are the Black Panthers?", 1968 September 7; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Author: Robert Bailey. Published in "Human Events" magazine.
  - "Where Are the Clark Kents of Yesteryear? They Are Infiltrating the Movement, and Here Is How to Get Rid of Them", 1970; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Reprinted from "Ramparts" magazine and distributed by RESIST.
  - "Which Side Are YOU On?", 1974 June; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Published for The League for Proletarian Revolution by Red Star Publications.
    New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; League for Proletarian Revolution
  - "Which Way America? The Political Perspective of the Youth Section of the Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee", 1981; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Published by the Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee.
    Socialist Organizing Committee (Orange County, Calif.)
  - "White Supremacy and the Afro-American National Question", 1978; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Author: Don Hamerquist. Published by the Sojourner Truth Organization.
  - "Why Khruschchov Fell", 1964; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - "Why Kill and Be Killed in Vietnam?" Flyer, undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Published by the Afro-American Committee To End the War In Vietnam.
  - "With the New People's Army in the Philippines", 1998; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "Women: The Longest Revolution", undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Author: Juliet Mitchell. Reprinted from the New Left Review by the Bay Area Radical Education Project.
  - "Women in American Society", 1972; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Authors: Ann D. Gordon, Mari Jo Buhle, and Nancy Schrom Dye. Originally published in the July-August 1971 issue of "Radical America" magazine.
    Women's rights; New Left
  - "Women and the Labor Movement", 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Authors: Sue Koritz and Lyn Meza. Published by the Massachusetts Trade Union Education League.
    Women's rights; National liberation movements; Trade Union Educational League (U.S.)
  - "Women's Liberation Must Fight U.S. Imperialism!", undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    Published by the Red Women's Detatchement of the Communist Party, USA (M-L)
    Women's rights; New Communist movement; Marxism-Leninism; Communist Party of the United States of America
  - "Workers Armed Defense Groups", undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - "Workers, Peasants and Soldiers Criticize Lin Piao and Confucius", 1976; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "Workers Viewpoint" Journal, undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - "Working on Two Levels", undated; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    Sojourner Truth Organization
  - "Workplace Papers", 1980; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - World Mother's Day Assembly, 1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Yale Grad Collective Flyer, undated; Series 2 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Student movements; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements -- United States
  - "Yankee Refugee: West Coast Newsletter of American Exiles", 1968-1969; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Young Communist League Celebration, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Communist Party of the United States of America; Young Communist League of the U.S.
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1991; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Pamphlets by title: New Left [arrangement chronological], 1972-1996; Series 5
  Arranged chronological.
  This series is composed of various printed material, including pamphlets, newspapers, newsletters, journals and flyers, produced by and about radical left-wing organizations and issues dating from 1972-1996. Most of the materials date from the New Left era, between the years of 1960 and 1980.
  Further, the materials were published by and about a wide range of organizations, from Maoist and Marxist-Leninist communist factions, to Black Power organizations, to student groups. Among others, these include the Black Panther Party, the Black Workers Congress, Students for a Democratic Society, the Weather Underground, the Industrial Workers of the World, the Revolutionary Union and Revolutionary Communist Party, USA.
  - People's Canada News, 1972 January - August; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - People's Canada News, 1973 March - April; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - People's Canada News, 1973 May; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - People's Canada News, 1973 June; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - People's Canada News, 1973 August - September; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - People's Canada News, 1973 October - November; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - People's Canada News, 1973 December; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - People's Canada News, 1974 January - February; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - People's Canada News, 1974 March - April; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - People's Canada News, 1974 May - October; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - People's Canada News, 1974 October; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - People's Canada News, 1975 February - November; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - The Worker, 1973 April 13; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - American revolutionary youth campaign conference of North American Marxist-Leninist, 1973 August -September; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Rhode Island student advance! vols 1-3, 1972-1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Revolution May Day supplement, 1974 May; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - New solidarity national caucus of labor committee vol 4, 1973 April; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - African voices: organ of the African progressive study group vo. 2, 1973 March - July; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Chingari liberation vol. 4 - 5, 1971-1973; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Conference of North American Marxist-Leninist Buffalo NY, 1973 August 18 - September 02; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Chingari vols. 3-6, 1970-1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Voice over-the-Rhine community newspaper, 1974 August; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Canadian student movement 'organise to change the world!", Circa 1973 December 26-31; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - People's tribune special supplement vol 2 no. 4, 1973 July; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Guardian independent radical newsweekly, 1973 May 16; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - North American news service, 1972 October 1 - December 15; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - North American news service, 1973 March 25 - July 1; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - North American news service, 1973 July 02 - December 09; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - North American news service, 1974 January 08 - April 07; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - The Marxist-Leninist Party of Canada resolutely supports the worker's struggles on the economic front, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - The Black liberation struggle the Black workers congress and proletarian revolution by the Black Workers Congress, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Internal bulletin central organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists report of the second meeting of the National Committee of the Central Organization of the U.S. Marxist-Leninists, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Hail the 4th anniversary of Chairman Mao's May 20th statement, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - The red papers by the revolutionary union nos. 5, 7, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - The red papers by the revolutionary union no. 6, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Marxism and feminism by Charnie Guettel, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Toward ideological clarity by Imamu Amiri Baraka, 1974; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Revolution and the Australian state: Australia's revolution: looking backward: looking forward; imperialism in Australia by E.F. Hill, Undated; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Class struggle journal of communist thought Spring #1, 1975; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Dragon published by Bay Area Research Collective Nos. 4, 7, 1975-1976; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Hursel Alexander: early recollections, 1976; Series 5 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Memories of building the UAW by J.S. Napier, 1976; Series 5 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Stalin, Marxism-Leninism and the Lef* by Russell Jacoby, 1976; Series 5 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - The communist: theoretical journal of the Central Committee of the Revolutionary Communist Party Vol. 1 No. 2, 1977 May 01; Series 5 (Box 59, Folder 3)